const List<Map<String, dynamic>> CSSQuestions = [
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are ways to add CSS to an HTML document?",
    "options": [
      "A. Inline style",
      "B. External style sheet",
      "C. Internal style sheet",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are valid CSS selectors?",
    "options": [
      "A. Element selectors",
      "B. Class selectors",
      "C. ID selectors",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid CSS property?",
    "options": [
      "A. text-color",
      "B. font-size",
      "C. text-align",
      "D. Both B and C"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. Both B and C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which elements are block-level elements?",
    "options": [
      "A. span",
      "B. div",
      "C. img",
      "D. strong"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. div"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which value can be used with the CSS display property?",
    "options": [
      "A. inline",
      "B. block",
      "C. flex",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are valid color formats in CSS?",
    "options": [
      "A. CMYK",
      "B. HSL",
      "C. RGB",
      "D. Both B and C"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. Both B and C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which property is used to style fonts in CSS?",
    "options": [
      "A. font-style",
      "B. font-size",
      "C. font-family",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which property is used to set the background color?",
    "options": [
      "A. background-color",
      "B. bg-color",
      "C. background",
      "D. background-image"
    ],
    "Answer": "A. background-color"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a positioning value in CSS?",
    "options": [
      "A. static",
      "B. center",
      "C. fixed",
      "D. Both A and C"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. Both A and C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are part of the CSS box model?",
    "options": [
      "A. Padding",
      "B. Border",
      "C. Margin",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are Flexbox properties?",
    "options": [
      "A. flex-direction",
      "B. flex-wrap",
      "C. justify-content",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid CSS transition property?",
    "options": [
      "A. transition-duration",
      "B. transition-style",
      "C. transition-type",
      "D. transition-color"
    ],
    "Answer": "A. transition-duration"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid CSS animation property?",
    "options": [
      "A. @keyframes",
      "B. animation-duration",
      "C. animation-timing-function",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are ways to add CSS to an HTML document?",
    "options": [
      "A. Inline style",
      "B. External style sheet",
      "C. Internal style sheet",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are valid CSS selectors?",
    "options": [
      "A. Element selectors",
      "B. Class selectors",
      "C. ID selectors",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid CSS property?",
    "options": [
      "A. text-color",
      "B. font-size",
      "C. text-align",
      "D. Both B and C"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. Both B and C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which elements are block-level elements?",
    "options": [
      "A. span",
      "B. div",
      "C. img",
      "D. strong"
    ],
    "Answer": "B. div"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which value can be used with the CSS display property?",
    "options": [
      "A. inline",
      "B. block",
      "C. flex",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are valid color formats in CSS?",
    "options": [
      "A. CMYK",
      "B. HSL",
      "C. RGB",
      "D. Both B and C"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. Both B and C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which property is used to style fonts in CSS?",
    "options": [
      "A. font-style",
      "B. font-size",
      "C. font-family",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which property is used to set the background color?",
    "options": [
      "A. background-color",
      "B. bg-color",
      "C. background",
      "D. background-image"
    ],
    "Answer": "A. background-color"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a positioning value in CSS?",
    "options": [
      "A. static",
      "B. center",
      "C. fixed",
      "D. Both A and C"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. Both A and C"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are part of the CSS box model?",
    "options": [
      "A. Padding",
      "B. Border",
      "C. Margin",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are Flexbox properties?",
    "options": [
      "A. flex-direction",
      "B. flex-wrap",
      "C. justify-content",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid CSS transition property?",
    "options": [
      "A. transition-duration",
      "B. transition-style",
      "C. transition-type",
      "D. transition-color"
    ],
    "Answer": "A. transition-duration"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a valid CSS animation property?",
    "options": [
      "A. @keyframes",
      "B. animation-duration",
      "C. animation-timing-function",
      "D. All of the above"
    ],
    "Answer": "D. All of the above"
  },
];
